KERRY: My relationship with my son,
Phillip whilst we as parents didn't
really understand the autism and the
impacts of the autism very well, that
was very challenging when he was younger.
But then once the relationship development
intervention helped us to understand
that better and our role in it better as
communicators and interactors if you like.
Then my relationship with
Philip has gotten much better.
And, I mean I think what I would say about
that as a journey is that it has taught
me an awful lot about, well it's helped
me to learn an awful lot about autism.
And having the relationship with
Philip has made me look at life in a
different way, which is a positive thing.
And also I think it has made a big
difference to my own ability to
become a better person, actually.
So yeah, I think that's what, certainly,
one of the things that has happened
to me as a result of my relationship
with Philip, I do think it's made
me into a better person and, you
know, that can only be a good thing
whilst it's been a hard journey.